Without a passport,
如果没有护照，
and attempted to bribe the public servants
并试图贿赂公务员
I suspect you are scheming
我怀疑你有阴谋
engage in illegal activities
从事非法活动
come!
来！
Bring them down.
把他们打倒。
Search them.
搜查他们。
Get down. Come down.
下来。坠落。
Come down.
坠落。
Two knives have been found.
已发现两把刀。
Captain Zhao,
Captain Zhao,
and brought an unregistered firearm.
并携带了一把未注册的枪支。
You are doubly guilty
你有双重罪
detective
侦探
you know my job
你知道我的工作
It's for self-defense
这是为了自卫
we never cause trouble in the concession.
我们从不在租界制造麻烦。
Captain Zhao,
Captain Zhao,
you don't know anything?
你什么都不知道吗？
French Concession is flooded with guns recently
法租界最近枪支泛滥
many murders recently.
最近发生了很多谋杀案。
Wen Wei Wei's Evening News,
Wen Wei Wei's Evening News,
got thrown by hand grenades.
被手榴弹扔了。
How come you brought so many weapons?
你怎么带了这么多武器？
How can you say that you're not here to make trouble?
你怎么能说你不是来闹事的呢？
It was done by No. 76.
这是76号完成的。
It has nothing to do with us.
这与我们无关。
I'm a businessman.
我是商人。
I can do small business.
我可以做点小生意。
For business.
商业用途。
That won't be a problem.
那不会有问题的。
Come with me
跟我来
come with me to the police station to register
跟我去警察局登记
you can get a passport
你可以获得护照
It's urgent.
这很紧急。
Just a excuse.
只是一个借口。
You'll need me next time.
下次你会需要我的。
Make an exception.
破例。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Alright.
好吧。
Brothers.
兄弟。
Listen up, I'll tell you.
听着，我告诉你。
This is my good buddy.
这是我的好哥们。
Don't handcuff them later.
以后别给他们戴上手铐。
Got it?
知道了？
Got it.
知道了。
You are accommodating enough?
你够包容吗？
Take her away.
带她走。
Just go.
去吧。
I'll leave on my own.
我会自己离开。
Come on.
快点。
Take them inside.
带他们进去。
Hello
你好
sheriff Clement.
警长克莱门特.
Come on.
快点。
Brother.
兄弟。
I think I've seen this foreigner before.
我想我以前见过这个外国人。
Come to register.
快来报名吧。
Whose dagger is it?
匕首是谁的？
It's mine.
这是我的。
What's your name?
你叫什么名字？
Two Swords.
两把剑。
Wang Hanlong!
王汉龙！
Where's the spear?
矛在哪里？
Zhao An.
Zhao An.
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Your bag.
你的包。
There are personal letters inside.
里面有私人信件。
Please take them.
请带走它们。
This place is much safer than a bank.
这个地方比银行安全多了。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Hurry up!
赶快！
Take you to the detention room.
带你去拘留室。
Go, please.
请走吧。
Watch this.
看这个。
Where's the tag?
标签在哪里？
Why are you pushing me?
你为什么推我？
Are you out of your mind?
你是不是疯了？
Here you are.
给你。
Great.
伟大的。
This is broken.
这已破了。
This is sealed with pewter wax.
这是用锡蜡密封的。
How long will it take?
它需要多长时间？
Melt and take photos before cooling.
冷却前融化并拍照。
40 to 50 minutes.
40到50分钟。
I can hang on for 30 minutes at most.
我最多能坚持30分钟。
Do it as soon as possible.
尽快做。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
To fill out this form.
填写此表格。
And after that,
在那之后，
you can leave with a seal
你可以带着印章离开
and you can leave.
你可以离开了。
Come on.
快点。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Where is the pen?
笔在哪里？
A pen.
一支钢笔。
Pens?
钢笔？
You didn't bring any pens?
你没带笔吗？
You've collected the things
你已经收集了东西
oh, Detective Ye
哦，叶侦探
don't you have any pens?
你没有笔吗？
Sorry about that.
对于那个很抱歉。
Then...
然后...
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
I'll go and find you
我去找你
thank you for your hard work.
感谢你的努力工作。
Serving the public
服务大众
hurry up!
赶快！
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
Where is the water?
水在哪里？
Water?
水？
There's no water.
没有水了。
We had water in the morning.
我们早上有水。
We really ran out of water.
我们真的没水了。
There was still water in the morning.
早上起来还有水。
Stop it.
停下来。
There's only one pen.
只有一支笔。
Wait. That's impossible.
等待。这不可能。
There must be water.
必须有水。
Get another pen.
再拿一支笔。
Get a few more pens.
多拿几支笔。
Pens and caps.
钢笔和帽子。
Thank you.
谢谢。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
What kind of pen is this?
这是什么笔？
That's right.
这是正确的。
What pen?
什么笔？
I'm sure it's good this time.
我确信这次很好。
Hurry up.
赶快。
There, there.
那里，那里。
This...
这...
Detective
侦探
this is not something we should fill out
这不是我们应该填写的内容
aren't you going to stay in French Concession temporarily?
你不打算暂时住在法租界吗？
Who's staying here?
谁住在这里？
Why are we staying here?
我们为什么留在这里？
Detective
侦探
just passed by?
刚刚过去？
Just passed by in 20 minutes.
20分钟就过去了。
Just passing by.
只是路过而已。
Just 20 minutes?
只要20分钟？
Please, please.
拜托，拜托。
It's okay if you don't want to stay.
如果你不想留下来也没关系。
There's something wrong.
这里有些不对劲。
Sorry.
对不起。
Don't fill this out.
不要填写这个。
I'll get a stamp from the traffic department
我去交通部门盖个章
and get a seal on it.
并盖上印章。
Stop being embarrassing, okay?
别再尴尬了好吗？
Can you hurry up?
你能快点吗？
Brother.
兄弟。
Scram!
滚！
Stop pacing in front of me.
别在我面前踱步了。
Alright?
好吧？
All right.
好的。
Scram!
滚！
Chief.
首席。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
What?
什么？
-Don't touch me, right? -Is that enough?
-别碰我，好吗？-够了吗？
Alright, alright.
好吧好吧。
Don't talk to me!
别跟我说话！
Do you have guns?
你有枪吗？
You just left?
你刚刚离开？
That's right.
这是正确的。
Captain Zhao. Leader Zhao.
Captain Zhao. Leader Zhao.
You reminded me, Captain Zhao.
赵队长你提醒我了。
If you bring guns,
如果你带枪的话
you have to fill in
你必须填写
weapons Permit Application Form. Captain Zhao.
武器许可证申请表。赵队长。
Do you think that's enough?
你认为这就足够了吗？
Chief Zhao.
Chief Zhao.
Please wait.
请稍等。
Wait!
等待！
I'm running out of time.
我的时间不多了。
If this goes on,
如果再这样下去，
If we can't make it to the meeting,
如果我们不能参加会议
If we can't
如果我们不能
hand the file to Kimura,
将文件交给木村，
we will be dead.
我们会死的。
Please.
请。
It's not our brothers.
这不是我们的兄弟。
It was you.
是你。
Brother.
兄弟。
Aren't you my younger brother?
你不是我弟弟吗？
Tell me that
告诉我
Is he really my brother?
他真的是我弟弟吗？
That's right.
这是正确的。
If you deny it,
如果你否认的话
I'll shoot you to death.
我会开枪打死你。
It's my fault.
我的错。
That's right.
这是正确的。
Darn it!
该死的！
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
I followed the rules.
我遵守规则。
Don't be angry with me.
别生我的气。
That's useless.
那是没用的。
Keep that in mind.
记住这一点。
Seal it
密封起来
on the ceremony.
仪式上。
Almost done
快完成了
or is she really shy?
或者她真的很害羞吗？
This application form
这份申请表
needs Chief Li's signature
需要李科长签字
but Section Chief Li is not here
但李科长不在
you'll have to wait a bit.
你需要稍等一下。
It'll be soon.
很快就会的。
Hold on.
坚持，稍等。
Brother.
兄弟。
That's not right.
那是不对的。
Something is wrong with him.
他有些不对劲。
That's right.
这是正确的。
He's got serious problems.
他有严重的问题。
We're working for the Japanese,
我们为日本人工作，
and he works for the French?
他为法国人工作？
Are all dogs.
都是狗。
Why are you making things difficult for us?
你为什么要为难我们？
Brother,
兄弟，
I remembered that
我记得
where I met that foreigner.
我在那里遇见了那个外国人。
How is it?
如何？
The horse is riding.
马正在骑马。
They can't be suppressed.
他们无法被压制。
Waiting for it to cool down.
等待它冷却。
A few minutes.
几分钟。
This is the French Concession,
这里是法租界，
you can't go in there
你不能进去
get out of our way.
别挡我们的路。
Captain Zhao
Captain Zhao
section Chief Li will be right back
李科长马上回来
captain Zhao.
captain Zhao.
Inspector Clermont.
克莱蒙督察。
I'm from Taihe Trading Firm.
我是泰和商行的。
You may not know me,
你可能不认识我，
but I know that
但我知道
you bought two boxes of opium ointment from me.
你从我这里买了两盒鸦片膏。
Near the Archbishop Road.
靠近大主教路。
Do you remember that?
你是否记得？
Sheriff Clement.
克莱门特警长。
The man broke into the concession with a weapon
该男子持武器闯入租界
I am going through the formalities for him.
我正在帮他办理手续。
Close the door.
关门。
Yes
是的
this is Captain Zhao.
这是赵队长。
He is my good friend.
他是我的好朋友。
You're mistaken
你错了
return his things to him immediately.
立即将东西归还给他。
And send him back to the parking lot.
并把他送回停车场。
Yes
是的
thank you, Clement.
谢谢你，克莱门特。
Sheriff Clermans.
克莱曼斯警长。
I'll get the car key in my room.
我去房间拿车钥匙。
Captain Zhao is in a rush.
赵队长急了。
Drive my car.
开我的车。
And help him clean it up.
并帮他清理干净。
Come on.
快点。
Take out my things.
把我的东西拿出来。
Hurry up!
赶快！
Return Captain Zhao's things to him.
把赵队长的东西还给他。
Thank you, Clement.
谢谢你，克莱门特。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Take a look
看一看
are your things still there?
你的东西还在吗？
They are.
他们是。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
When were you early?
你什么时候早到的？
Two o'clock.
两点了。
We'll be late. Let's go!
我们快迟到了。我们走吧！
Brother!
兄弟！
Gun. Gun.
枪。枪。
It won't be as fast as my car.
它不会像我的车那么快。
Hey!
嘿！
Here they are.
他们来了。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Where's the car?
车在哪儿？
Slowly.
慢慢地。
Can I drive?
我可以开车？
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
See you later.
回头见。
The bride's feet can't touch the ground.
新娘的脚不能接触地面。
The groom has to carry the bride off the carriage.
新郎必须把新娘从马车上抱下来。
Good.
好的。
I can carry everything.
我可以承载一切。
What do you mean by "carry everything"?
“携带一切”是什么意思？
As if I'm so fat.
好像我很胖一样。
I didn't mean that.
我不是那个意思。
I was wrong.
我错了。
I hope my bride
我希望我的新娘
could give me a lifetime
可以给我一生
to make up for my mistakes.
来弥补我的错误。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I want to hold you.
我想抱你。
And if I do not see your face
如果我看不到你的脸
If I don't see your face.
如果我看不到你的脸。
From now on,
今后，
I don't want to miss every expression on your face.
我不想错过你脸上的每一个表情。
I will share your happiness
我会分享你的快乐
and sorrow,
和悲伤，
with you,
与你，
and sorrow.
和悲伤。
Married!
已婚！
Have you got a plan?
你有计划吗？
How do you plan to kill the warrior under the mountain?
你打算如何杀死山下的武者？
A serrated knife.
一把锯齿刀。
The warrior will be killed with a serrated knife.
战士将被锯齿刀杀死。
What's the plan?
计划是什么？
Where is the knife hidden?
刀藏在哪里？
When to start it.
什么时候开始呢。
And how to evacuate later.
以及之后如何撤离。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
I've arranged everything.
我已经安排好了一切。
After your operation is successful,
手术成功后，
go to Pier 16
前往 16 号码头
I'll wait for you there.
我会在那里等你。
I'll arrange the boat
我来安排船
and send you to Jiaxing for temporary shelter.
并送你到嘉兴暂住。
When you finish the mission,
当你完成任务后，
you can kill this traitor!
你可以杀了这个叛徒！
Brother!
兄弟！
Where's Kun?
坤在哪儿？
He's locked in the storage room on the second floor.
他被锁在二楼的储藏室里。
There is a window there
那里有一扇窗户
where you can overlook the whole scene.
在那里你可以俯瞰整个场景。
Take me there.
带我到那里。
Alright.
好吧。
When!
什么时候！
Later you'll see
稍后你会看到
your beloved woman
你心爱的女人
Is going to marry another man.
即将嫁给另一个男人。
A traitor and dog you hate the most.
你最讨厌的叛徒和狗。
It's fine.
没关系。
When you see it,
你看到它的时候，
you think about it if it's worth it?
你想一想是否值得？
You protected
你保护了
to protect a woman
为了保护一个女人
a woman who betrayed your faith?
背叛你信仰的女人？
To betray your people?
背叛你的人民？
The Commander below the mountain.
山下的指挥官。
Kun was taken to the wedding venue by us.
Kun被我们带到了婚礼场地。
If Kun and Zuo Shuangtao are together,
如果坤和左双涛在一起的话
left Shuangtao must have had contact with you at the scene.
左双桃肯定在现场与你有过接触。
That's why...
这就是为什么...
We've placed the snipers on the second floor
我们把狙击手安置在二楼
keep an eye on Left Shuangtao at all times
时刻关注左双桃
to make sure you're not in danger.
以确保您没有危险。
You still need to be aware of
你还需要注意
for Shan Ren.
for Shan Ren.
That day.
那天。
And there are reporters on the scene.
并且现场还有记者。
It's a bad influence to us.
对我们来说影响不好。
Once we confirm that Left Shuangtao is the assassin,
一旦我们确认左双桃就是凶手，
settle it after the wedding.
婚礼之后再解决。
Yes
是的
there's one thing.
有一件事。
I don't know if you've heard.
不知道你有没有听说过。
The Prime Minister of the Guards
近卫军首相
seeking peace talks with Chongqing.
寻求与重庆和谈。
Peace talks?
和平会谈？
Chiang Kai-shek has retreated to Chongqing.
蒋介石已撤退到重庆。
He can't compete with us at all.
他根本无法与我们竞争。
We can negotiate under such circumstances.
在这种情况下我们可以进行谈判。
If we want to continue our war in East Asia,
如果我们想继续我们在东亚的战争
and then a war against the US will be inevitable.
那么与美国的战争将不可避免。
The Prime Minister is under pressure
首相面临压力
to end the East Asian War as soon as possible
尽快结束东亚战争
and keep what we've achieved.
并保持我们所取得的成就。
In that case,
在这种情况下，
the influence of our military
我军的影响力
our military's influence.
我军的影响力。
Exactly.
确切地。
We must try our best
我们必须尽力
to make the peace talk end in failure.
使和谈以失败告终。
I leave the task
我离开任务
Is entrusted to you.
就托付给你了。
Yes
是的
today, I, Chen Jiaping,
today, I, Chen Jiaping,
officially marries Zuo Shuangtao.
officially marries Zuo Shuangtao.
I will always be loyal to you,
我将永远忠诚于你
love you, believe in you,
爱你，相信你，
to take care of you.
照顾你。
Come here.
过来。
And take care of you.
并照顾你。
And be with each other for the rest of our lives.
并与彼此共度余生。
Come.
来。
This way, please.
这边请。
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
Let me report something to you.
让我向您报告一件事。
What you ordered
您订购的商品
I've arranged it.
我已经安排好了
We must keep this
我们必须保留这个
you must keep this a secret.
你必须保守秘密。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
Feng Qi is reliable
冯琪可靠
and tight-lipped.
并且守口如瓶。
Have mutual affinity
有缘分
section Chief Chen
陈科长
captain Zhao.
captain Zhao.
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm a little nervous.
我有点紧张。
Are you memorizing lyrics?
你背歌词吗？
Thank you.
谢谢。
It's a wedding
这是一场婚礼
chief Chen, seriously
陈局长认真的
you look like a decent man
你看上去是个正派的人
In this suit.
穿着这套衣服。
Right?
正确的？
Right.
正确的。
That's right.
这是正确的。
What Captain Zhao
赵队长什么
I always learn about
我总是了解
has always been what I learn from.
一直是我学习的对象。
And good taste.
而且味道好。
Thank you, Captain Zhao.
谢谢赵队长。
The banquet is about to begin.
宴会即将开始。
I'm not hungry.
我不饿。
OK.
好的。
Alright.
好吧。
It hasn't started yet.
事情还没有开始。
Why are you drinking?
你为什么喝酒？
Fang Fang,
Fang Fang,
I'll drink with you.
我和你一起喝酒。
She's beautiful
她很漂亮
section Chief Chen is so lucky
陈科长真幸运
any woman is beautiful
任何女人都是美丽的
every woman is not beautiful.
每个女人都不是美丽的。
That's not necessarily the case.
情况不一定如此。
Sometimes,
有时，
It's more important to get married than to dress nicely
结婚比穿得漂亮更重要
than a beautiful bride.
比美丽的新娘。
Did you see that?
你看到了吗？
Have you seen Zuo Shuangtao?
Have you seen Zuo Shuangtao?
This is the woman you love.
这就是你爱的女人。
Right?
正确的？
Who are you referring to?
你指的是谁？
I don't know her at all.
我根本不认识她。
Such an act?
这样的行为？
You know what?
你知道吗？
This woman is going to sleep
这个女人要睡觉了
Is going to sleep with another man tonight.
今晚要和另一个男人睡。
I don't believe that.
我不相信。
That you don't have any feelings at all?
难道你就一点感觉都没有吗？
Go out and have a drink.
出去喝一杯。
I'll watch the movie with Kun.
我会和坤一起看电影。
Next, let the groom
接下来就让新郎
and bride
和新娘
exchange rings
交换戒指
from today on,
从今天，
I will be loyal...
我会忠诚...
To love you forever,
想要永远爱你，
and to trust you
并相信你
to help you,
来帮你，
and take good care of you.
并照顾好你。
What about you?
你呢？
Is indeed imperfect.
确实是不完美的。
But of course,
但是当然，
I'm not perfect either.
我也不完美。
But the two of us will
但我们两个人会
that'll be perfect.
那会很完美。
Alright.
好吧。
Master.
掌握。
The boat is ready.
船已经准备好了。
We are ready.
我们准备好了。
We can leave any time.
我们可以随时离开。
Alright.
好吧。
When will the person you are talking about come?
你说的那个人什么时候会来？
She will come.
她会来的。
When!
什么时候！
Are you feeling pain right now?
你现在感到疼痛吗？
And shamed?
还羞愧吗？
Take this away.
把这个拿走。
Are you still going to protect this woman?
你还要保护这个女人吗？
I don't want to see it anymore.
我不想再看到它了。
Please.
请。
A serrated knife.
一把锯齿刀。
There's no serrated knife.
没有锯齿刀。
Next, I'll have the bride and groom
接下来，我请新娘和新郎
to cut the cake for you.
为你切蛋糕。
He shared their sweetness
他分享了他们的甜蜜
to everyone here.
给这里的每个人。
On such an important occasion,
在如此重要的时刻，
we'd like to invite Mr. Murayama
我们想邀请村山先生
to cut the happy cake with us.
和我们一起切快乐蛋糕。
When.
什么时候。
I can understand you.
我能理解你。
Just tell me
就告诉我嘛
If Zuo Shuangtao is
If Zuo Shuangtao is
and assassinate Martial Master of the Mountain Below?
并刺杀山下武师？
I promise
我保证
to spare your life.
饶你一命。
That's not right.
那是不对的。
Not only will I spare your life,
我不仅会饶你一命，
I can't forgive
我无法原谅
for the past.
在过去的。
Alright?
好吧？
Let bygones be bygones
过去的就让它过去吧
I want to see the warrior under the mountain.
我想看看山下的武士。
It's the same if you told me.
如果你告诉我的话也是一样的。
I want to see him alone.
我想单独见他。
This way, please.
这边请。
The Grand Commander of the Lower Hill.
下山大统帅。
I'll be at the gate
我会在门口
call me anytime.
随时给我打电话。
Now we're the only two left.
现在只剩下我们两个了。
What do you want to say?
你想说什么？
What is it?
它是什么？
Untie me first.
先给我解开。
I'm already in this state.
我已经处于这个状态了。
You have a gun,
你有枪，
It is your men outside.
外面是你的人。
You still worry that I'll kill you?
你还担心我会杀了你吗？
All right.
好的。
What do you want to tell me?
你想告诉我什么？
What's it?
那是什么？
I told you.
我告诉你了。
What's in it for me?
这对我有什么好处？
You can get some reward.
你可以获得一些奖励。
And leave here safely.
并且安全离开这里。
Certainly,
当然，
If you're willing to give it up,
如果你愿意放弃的话
you can be
你可以
you can be the team leader.
你可以成为团队的领导者。
At the same time, you'll receive a large settlement fund.
同时，您将收到一大笔结算资金。
Dear guests,
尊敬的客人，
It's almost eight o'clock.
已经快八点了。
The most exciting moment
最激动人心的时刻
of the wedding.
婚礼的。
Please raise your head and look to the sky now.
现在请抬起头来看看天空。
The firework show.
烟花表演。
Mr. Only.
仅先生。
The Chief of Shanghai District, Wang Tianmu,
上海市区长王天木，
zhao Gangyi from Qingdao Station
zhao Gangyi from Qingdao Station
and Pei San of Tianjin Railway Station.
和天津火车站的裴三。
Their level is much higher than yours.
他们的水平比你高得多。
That's why they're alive.
这就是他们还活着的原因。
We're the same, aren't we?
我们是一样的，不是吗？
What are you worried about?
你担心什么？
Why don't you leave Shanghai?
你为什么不离开上海？
When I close my eyes,
当我闭上眼睛时，
I was seeing Xiao Hu and Da Xuan.
我正在见到小胡和大轩。
How am I supposed to leave?
我该如何离开？
I want to stay to take revenge.
我想留下来报仇。
And kill them.
并杀死他们。
To get the secret letter back.
为了拿回那封密信。
But I don't know what to do.
但我不知道该怎么办。
Can you help me think of a way?
你能帮我想想办法吗？
I have one solution,
我有一个解决方案，
however...
然而...
What?
什么？
Requires you to make a huge sacrifice.
需要你做出巨大的牺牲。
I'm not afraid to die.
我不怕死亡。
Tell me what to do.
告诉我该怎么做。
First, you need to be caught by Zhao An.
首先，你需要被赵安抓住。
And make sure they don't suspect
并确保他们不会怀疑
of your arrest.
你被捕的消息。
What about after he was arrested?
被捕后呢？
Did you see the number on it?
你看到上面的号码了吗？
Zhao An read my information.
赵安看了我的信息。
He will definitely find out
他一定会发现的
has something to do with
有关系
he will suspect
他会怀疑
why is my birthday engraved
为什么我的生日被刻上
on the pendant you carry?
在你携带的吊坠上？
The only explanation
唯一的解释
Is that you like me.
是不是你喜欢我。
Then we can get the hook.
然后我们就可以得到钩子了。
Alright.
好吧。
But you have to remember,
但你必须记住，
don't do anything until eight o'clock.
八点之前不要做任何事。
What's wrong, Guoguo?
果果怎么了？
Give me a hug.
抱抱我。
Don't speak.
别说话。
Just for a while
只是一会儿
jiaping,
jiaping,
I need to use the bathroom.
我需要上一趟洗手间。
Okay, I'll go with you.
好吧，我跟你一起去。
No need.
不需要。
You have to take care of everyone here.
你必须照顾这里的每个人。
Alright.
好吧。
Go and be back quickly.
快去吧，快点回来。
Mr. Yamashita.
山下先生。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Mr. Foot the mountain.
先生下山。
Mr. Underfoot.
脚下先生。
Captain Zhao.
Captain Zhao.
Commander Yamashita.
山下司令。
Under the mountain
山下
captain Zhao.
captain Zhao.
What's wrong with Mr. Yamashita?
山下先生怎么了？
He was assassinated.
他被暗杀了。
Commander!
指挥官！
Then ask for help!
然后寻求帮助！
I'll stop the bleeding.
我来止血。
Hurry.
匆忙。
Got stabbed.
被刺伤了
Hurry to send her to the hospital for rescue!
赶紧送她去医院抢救吧！
First aid?
急救？
Jerk!
混蛋！
Go after Kun now!
赶紧去追坤吧！
Yes
是的
come on.
快点。
What's going on?
这是怎么回事？
I didn't know.
我不知道。
I saw him like this the moment I came.
我一来就看到他这个样子。
Left Pair Tao.
左双涛。
Why are you here?
你为什么在这？
I went to the bathroom
我去了洗手间
I heard gunshots
我听到枪声
and someone's shouting.
有人在喊叫。
I came running right away.
我立刻就跑了过来。
Why did it go faster than us?
为什么它跑得比我们快？
The toilet is close to here
厕所离这里很近
aren't you afraid of gunshots?
你不怕枪声吗？
And you'll come back?
你会回来吗？
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
This is my wedding.
这是我的婚礼。
The most important moment in a woman's life.
女人一生中最重要的时刻。
Someone fired shots in my wedding.
有人在我的婚礼上开枪。
Should I hide?
我应该隐藏吗？
Or rush at him and kill him?
还是冲上去杀了他？
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
This may be a misunderstanding.
这可能是一个误会。
Cordon off the scene
现场拉起警戒线
no one is allowed to leave.
任何人都不准离开。
Yes
是的
are you all right?
你没事儿吧？
Hide in the utility room on the first floor
躲在一楼杂物间
I hid my military uniform there.
我把我的军装藏在那里。
Nobody move!
没人动！
I will kill whoever moves.
谁敢动我就杀了谁。
Just now Colonel Yamashita
刚才山下大佐
he lost
他输了
a very important item.
一个非常重要的项目。
Every one of you is a suspect.
你们每个人都是嫌疑人。
Search!
搜索！
I really don't have one.
我真的没有。
No, I...
不，我...
Do you still want to take off your clothes?
你还想脱衣服吗？
I took nothing.
我什么也没拿。
Don't look at them.
别看他们。
I told you.
我告诉你了。
I'll kill whoever moves.
谁敢动我就杀了谁。
Left Shuangtao.
Left Shuangtao.
You were the closest to Commander Shanxia.
你是与山下司令最亲近的人。
Who are you
你是谁
I'm on a mission with Zuo Shuangtao.
我和左双涛一起执行任务。
My name is Kun.
我叫坤。
We're on a mission together.
我们肩负着共同的使命。
Where is Left Shuangtao?
左双桃在哪里？
She asked me to come and find you
她让我来找你
you will arrange for me to evacuate.
你会安排我撤离。
Have you completed your mission?
你完成你的使命了吗？
I already killed Yamashita.
我已经杀了山下了。
Where is she?
她在哪？
Although Yamashita died,
虽然山下死了，
I didn't get the secret letter yet.
我还没有收到密信。
We know her well.
我们很了解她。
She won't leave.
她不会离开。
This is outrageous.
这太离谱了。
She still has no discipline in her eyes
她眼里依然没有纪律
Is she organized?
她有组织吗？
But I have to say that
但我不得不说
zuo Shuangtao is very predictable.
左双涛很有预见性。
Both Yamashita and Zhao An were tricked by her.
山下和赵安都被她给骗了。
I can arrange for you to hide in a safe place.
我可以安排你躲到安全的地方。
We'll meet Zuo Shuangtao when she gets the secret message.
等左双涛收到密信我们就去见她。
And find a way to leave Shanghai.
并想办法离开上海。
Hand...
手...
Stretch your hands.
伸出你的双手。
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
Nothing.
没有什么。
Take off your clothes.
脱掉你的衣服。
This...
这...
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
The thing you mentioned
你提到的事情
Is definitely not with Zuo Shuangtao.
绝对不是和左双涛在一起。
As your family.
作为你的家人。
Can you make an exception?
你能破例吗？
Zuo Shuangtao and I
Zuo Shuangtao and I
got married today.
今天结婚了。
As a husband,
作为丈夫，
I also want to save my wife's face.
我也想保住我老婆的面子。
I will serve the empire twice in the future.
以后我还会两次为帝国效力。
Home safety! Home safe!
居家安全！平安到家！
Take off your clothes!
脱掉你的衣服！